Finding Aid for the Ernst Toch Papers PASC-M.0001
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence, Series 3.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Feb-Mar) (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Ormandy, Johnson, Bauer, Steinberg, Mottier, Bass, Temianka, Hilb, Klemperer, Munch, Heuss.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Mar) (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Hilb, England, Kramer, Kolisch, French, Lawrie, Strecker, Bass, Rutz.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Mar-Apr) (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Green, Strecker, Pasquier, Stokowski, Hilb, Reitz, Fraenkel, Steinfeld, Cowell, J.S. Trotter, Rota, Compinsky.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Apr) (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Hilb, Cowell, Colbert, Keilberth, Compinsky, Reiner, Trotter, Johnson, Barbirolli, Ansermet, Borciani, Leonard, Wallenstein, Leide-Tedesco, Abert, Steinberg, England.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Apr-May) (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: French, Hilb, Compinsky, Kramer, Kramer, Leinsdorf, Wallenstein, Schott, Green, Bauer.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (May) (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Schmid, Sandved, Braunschweig, Shuk, Werfel, Kramer, Leonard, Reidenbach, Guillard, Trotter, Compinsky, Hood.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (May-June) (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Shuk, Compinsky, England, Munch, Lopatnikoff, Wallenstein, Garrett, Halasz, Bauer, Kramer, Leinsdorf, Barbirolli.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (June) (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Items 176-200. Primary correspondents: Sunshine, Kramer, Hilb, Munch, Klemperer, Nissim, Fraenkel, Garrett, Englend, Kestenberg, Barbirolli, Sandved. ***missing as of 8/12/03***
  - Correspondence, 1953 (July) (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Goldsen, England, Trotters, Kempner, Kramer, Steinfeld, Munch, Compinsky, Hilb, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (July-Aug) (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Hilb, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Steinberg, Huntington Hartford Foundation, Gimpel, Leonard, Bass, Compinsky, Goldsen.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Aug) (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Hilb, Vincent, Compinsky, Temianka, Huntington Hartford, Kaus, Castelnuovo-Tedesco.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Aug-Sep) (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Manheim, Trotter, Vincent, French, Garrett, Huntington Hartford, Werfel, Byrnes, Hilb.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Sept) (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: Hilb, ASCAP, Byrnes, Robertson, England, Steinfeld, MacDowell, Sunshine, Tcherepnin.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Sep-Oct) (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Sunshine, Hilb, MacDowell, Reitz, Vincent, Manheim, Stokowski.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Oct-Nov) (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Sunshine, MacDowell, Steinfeld, Vincent, Schiff, Stillman, Reich, Steinfeld, Golschmann, French.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Nov-Dec) (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Items 176-218. Primary correspondents: Manheim, Rink, MacDowell, Gimpel, Coolidge, Golschmann, Steinfeld, Mottier, Whitney, Bass, French, Braunschweig, Korngold, Solomon, Compinsky.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Jan) (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Leeds, Schiller, Bauer, Elkan, Rutz, Ames, Steinfeld, Lawrie, Zylmann, Rink, Stolper, French, Sunshine, Forster, Golschmann, Broido, Lopatnikoff, Preves, Hilb, Manheim.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Jan-Feb) (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Copland, Ahamson, Levinger, Broido, Steinberg, Holmboe, Morgan, Braunschweig, Leeds, Bass, Stolper, Lawrie, Drolc, Bauer, Kerr, Cykler, Leeb, French, Sunshine, Vaughn.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Feb) (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Broido, Stolper, Munch, Braunschweig, Levinger, Bauer, Rink, Kratt, Steinberg, Ginastera, Copland, Vincent.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Feb-Mar) (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Braunschweig, Stolper, Morgan, Levinger, Rink-Weeden, Steinfeld, Kafer, Weingarten, French, Broido, Sunshine, Drolc, Hartford, Waddington, Rink, Low, Kratt.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Mar-Apr) (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: Cykler, Leide-Tedesco, Izant, Dorati, Gates, Rogers, Post, Leeds, Korn, Foss, Levinger, Rink, Kotula, Sunshine, Stolper, Robertson, Braunschweig, Stillman, French.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Apr) (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Kafer, Degener, Bauer, Levinger, Korn, Braunschweig, Leeds, French, Compinsky, Mills, Weschler, Kestenberg, Fraenkel, Mottier, Trotter, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mills, Stolper.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Apr-May) (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Dorati, MacDowell, Leide-Tedesco, Broido, Leeds, French, Strelizer, Grun, Levinger, Lewertoff, Mills, Braunschweig, Kestenberg, Forster, Stolper, Rink, Weiner, Hartford.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (May) (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Items 176-199. Primary correspondents: Levinger, Compinsky, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Braunschweig, Sunshine, Fabel, MacDowell, Strelizer, Lewertoff, Stolper, Rink, Ahamson, Leide-Tedesco, Mottier, Weiner.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (May-June) (Box 58, Folder 9)
    Items 200-224. Primary correspondents: Voxman, French, Kendall, Leide-Tedesco, Dorati, Gates, England, Hilb, Steinberg, Stolper, Leinsdorf, Degener, Weiner, Sunshine, Mitropoulos, Jorda.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (July) (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Kratt, French, Steinberg, Leinsdorf, Weschler, Stolper, Nissim, Lewertoff, England, Jacobsen, Friedman, Sunshine, Rink, Ames, Searchinger, Trotter.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (July-Aug) (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondence: Sunshine, Solomon, Elkan, Mahler-Werfel, Ames, Friedman, French, Stolper, Jacobsen, Korn, Rink-Weeden, Koussevitsky, Mogil, Katzin, Brisman, Wernick, Bacon, Hood, Spivacke.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Aug) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Mogil, Sunshine, Brauch, Boult, Weschler, Katzin, MacDowell, Stolper, Fabel, Boosey, Leeds, Cykler, Spivacke, Compinsky, Toldis.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Aug-Sep) (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Leeds, Sunshine, Trotter, Broido, Jacobsen, Mogil, Griller, Kempner, Mitropoulos, Toldis, Grun, Katzin, Stolper, Hendl, Shoenfeld, Mitchell, Fricsay, Jorda, Rink, Seder.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Sep) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: MacDowell, Leonard, Toldi, Fabel, Strobel, Katzin, Seder, Zoff, Compinsky, Hood, Byrns, Munch, Sunshine, Bard, Jacobsen, Stolper, Spivacke, Beer, Bass, Korn, Olga Heifetz.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Oct) (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Wangerin, Stolper, Grasso, Zelka, Jacobsen, Mottier, Bauer, French, Seder, Rink, Bard, Ames, Tcherepnin, Kratt, Paray, Mitchell, Trotter, Spivacke, Stone.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Oct-Nov) (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Seton, Beer, Broido, Stone, Rink, Ames, Bard, Grasso, Schauffler, Munch, Weiner, Hilsberg, Fraenkel, Seder, Ahamson, Krips, Golschman.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Nov-Dec) (Box 59, Folder 8)
    Items 176-221. Primary correspondents: Leinsdorf, Weiner, Seder, Stolper, Krips, Spivacke, Trotter, Hilsberg, Kendall, Leide-Tedesco, Elguther, Foote, Klein, Whitney, Dorati, Compinsky, Gold, Beer, Rink, MacDowell, Flors, French, Wall, Elfenbein, Wardle, Grasso, Allison, Vogelsang, Bass, Gould.
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Dec) (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondence: Klein, Mottiers, Bass, Creighton, Gould, Allison, Jacobsen, Beer, Criterion, Wardle, Vincent, Kazounoff, MacDowell, Levinger, Spivacke, Vogelsang, Grosso.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Jan) (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondence: Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Jorda, Trotter, Reitz, Steinberg, Broido, Flor, Dahl, Bacon, Klemperer, J.S. Trotter, Katzin, Vincent, Strecker.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Jan) (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: MacDowell, Giddens, Fricsay, Korn, Reiner, Katzin, Petrillo, Seefehlner, Weiner, Salthoft, Mottier, Golschmann, Harris, Stresemann, Bass, MacDowell.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Jan-Feb) (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondence: Grasso, Mueller, Flor, MacDowell, Wardle, Kazounoff, Levinger, Munch, Burk, Golschmann, Korn, Leonard.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Feb) (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary corrrespondents: Klein, Fraenkel, Korn, Burk, Steinfeld, Fricsay, Levinger, Ames, Krips, Stolper, Segal, Jorda, Katzin, MacDowell, Hirshmann.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Feb) (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondence: Klein, Flors, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Hilsberg, Paray, Mitchell, Levinger, MacDowell, Bass, Rebner, Leinsdorf, J.S. Trotter, England, Drolc, Whitney.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Feb) (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Segal, Hirschler, Keilberth, Perry, Flor, Allison, Johns, J.S. Trotter, Harris, Sinzheimer, Grasso, Klein, Levinger, Fraenkel, MacDowell, Bass, Albersheim.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Feb-Mar) (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Items 176-216. Primary correspondents: Dreifuss, MacDowell, Mottier, Levertoff, Martin, Asow, Solomon, Grasso, Bass, Levinger, Steinberg, Hagen, Thomas, Wangerin, Baker, Tuerckheim, Thomas.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Mar) (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Williams, Levinger, Izant, Weiner, Keilberth, Thomas, Grasso, Kalmus, Wangerin, Flor, Schott, Fabel.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Mar-Apr) (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Mottiers, Weiner, Katzin, Rink, Rink-Weeden, Golschmann, Jorda, Kostelanetz, Jacobsen, Hennon, Kubelik, Seefehlner.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Apr) (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Golschmann, Rebner, Steinfeld, Hennon, Grasso, Vincent, Wangerin, Whitney, Rink-Weeden, Katzin, MacDowell, Mitchell, Rink, Hagen, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Kostelanetz, French, Turkheim, Adler.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Apr-May) (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Moldenhauer, Steinberg, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Rink, L. Klemperer, Grasso, Whitney, Katzin, Seder, Jacobsen, Dorati, Cykler, Goldberg, Kotula, Pascuzzi.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (May) (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Items 101-130. Primary correspondents: Gould, Edward, Cykler, Pascuzzi, Bass, Moldenhauer, Temianka, Fricsay, Wangerin, Keilberth, Schmid, Kalmus, Grasso, Weiner, Seefehlner, Steinfeld, Hagen, Kubelik.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (May-June) (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Items 131-160. Primary correspondents: Seefehlner, Fabel, Moldenhauer, Trautmann, Borciani, Reich, Steinfeld, Rink, Seder, Kostelanetz, Mottier, Katzin, Kalmus.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (June-July) (Box 61, Folder 7)
    Items 161-190. Primary correspondents: Rink, Schmid, Broido, Dorian, Levinger, Strecker, Fabel, MacDowell, Kendall, Edwards, Elfenheim, Fricsay, Seder, Kostelanetz, French, Byrns, Grasso, Mannes, Grentzer.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (July-Aug) (Box 61, Folder 8)
    Items 191-220. Primary correspondents: Edward, Gotze, Kendall, Goslich, Seder, Loughborough, Byrns, Seidler, Seefehlner, Baum, Mann, MacDowell, Muller-Kray, Hempel, Strecker.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Aug) (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Items 1-29. Primary correspondents: Pillot, Langner, Leeb, Seder, Stillman, French, Adams, Gotze, Schroter, Beck, Hubner, Mann, Hyams, Cohen, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Sep) (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Items 30-60. Primary correspondents: Seder, Kempner, Mann, Nissim, MacDowell, Mottier, Grasso, Fricsay, Beck, Johns, Katzin, Pillot, Leeb, Dorian, Kendall, Bass, Loughborough, French.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Sep-Oct) (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Items 61-90. Primary correspondents: Goslich, Schroter, Seder, Dorian, Kempner, Grasso, Mann, Loughborough, Hempel, Moldenhauer, Edwards, Griller, Kalmus, Keyser, Aylen, Steinberg, Gaber.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Oct-Nov) (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Items 91-120. Primary correspondents: Edwards, Levinger, Temianka, Wallenstein, Loughborough, Griller, Steinberg, Grasso, Allison, Seder, Leide-Tedesco, Harris, Katzin, Holde, Gaber.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Nov) (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Items 121-150. Primary correspondents: Daniel, Grasso, Leide-Tedesco, Mottier, Byrns, Edwards, Aylen, Katzin, Holde, Lewando, Hilb, Moldenhauer, Boehm, Pillot, MacDowell, Stone.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Nov-Dec) (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Items 151-180. Primary correspondents: Kalmus, Starck, Wunsch, Lewertoff, Mann, Steinberg, Edwards, Grasso, Johns, Jacobsen, Rink-Weeden, Seder, Holmboe, Gatchell, MacDowell, Temianka, Dorati, Reitz, Kendall, Katzin.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Dec) (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Items 181-198. Primary correspondents: Allison, Kratt, Lewertoff, Steinberg, Clifton, Steinfeld, Bass, Kownatsky, Seefehlner, R. Trotter, J.S. Trotter, Kalmus, Grasso, Hirshman.
  - Correspondence, 1955 (n.d.) (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Items 199-215. Primary correspondents: Keilberth, Miller, Dorati, Hagen, Byrns, Gates, Harriet, Hartford, Holmboe, Flor, Steinberg, Zoff.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Jan) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Seder, Rink, Gomez, Whewell, Edwards, Johns, Leonard, Katzin, England, Roy, Kratt, Daniel, Sabon.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Jan) (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Havener, Solomon, Hargreaves, French, Stillman, Fricsay, Klemperer, England, Mottier, Salzman, Daniel, Seefehlner, Spivacke, Previtali.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Jan-Feb) (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: England, Tisilo, Seder, Auras, Steinfeld, Kalmus, Bass, Petrillo, Hirshman, Wilkinson, Golschmann, Wallenstein, Dorati, Spivacke, Rodosi.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Feb-Mar) (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Wuensch, Mottier, Laaf, Spivacke, Fricsay, Seefehlner, Sutkind, Dorati, Rebner, Kalmus, Rink-Weeden, Steinberg, Seder, Katzin.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (July) (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (July-Aug) (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Mar) (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: Katzin, Seefehlner, Munch, L.Klemperer, Jacobsen, Schroter, Stark, Bass, Spivacke, Keilberth, Beer, Sartori, MacDowell, Solomon, Steinberg, Hilb.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Mar-Apr) (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Spivacke, Wallenstein, Fineman, Mueller, Munch, Jacobsen, Hartmann, Liebermann, Sacher, Freccia, Marton, Mann, Wangerin, Sweeney, Daniel.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Apr-May) (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Sacher, Jaroschy, Manheim, Liebermann, Seefehlner, Spivacke, Jochum, Hilb, Dorati, Gotze, Drolc, Asow, England, MacDowell, Kalmus.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (May) (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Items 176-204. Primary correspondents: Freccia, Sacher, Stone, May, Fricsay, Hilb, Frohlich, Marton, Rollman-Branch, Sweeney, Mottier, Spivacke, Cunningham, Fassett, Beer, Weeden, Zoff.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (May) (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Items1-25. Primary correspondents: Seefehlner, Schott, Hilb, MacDowell, Fricasy, Aylen, Muench, Kalmus, Heuss, Liebermann.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (May-June) (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Liebermann, Daniel, Spivacke, Frohlich, Rehberg, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Temianka, Strecker, Pillot, Heuss, Rehberg, Lewertoff, Hargreaves.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (June-July) (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Freedman, Trotter, Jung, Sunshine, Beer, Mottier, Kestenbergg, Strecker, Bass, Kalmus, Rebner.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (July) (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Strecker, Freedman, Heilmann, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Auras, Rosbaud, Flor, Strobel, Reitz, Liebermann, Vincent.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (July-Aug) (Box 64, Folder 5)
    Items 101-130. Primary correspondents: Keilberth, Strobel, Strecker, Willner, Jung, Jones, Westerman, Sunshine, Mottier, Beinum, Dorati, Nissim.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Aug) (Box 64, Folder 6)
    Items 131-160. Primary correspondents: MacDowell, MiCastelnuovo-Tedesco, VIncent, Strecker, Pillot, Asow, Jung, Hilb, Westerman, French, Slater, Fraenkel.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Aug-Oct) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    Items 161-190. Primary correspondents: Sunshine, Westerman, Schott, French, Asow, Poduschka, Strecker, Hoch, WEsterman, Auras, Fricsay, Mills Music, Strobel.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Oct-Nov) (Box 64, Folder 8)
    Items 191-224. Primary correspondents: Slater, Rink, Dorati, Vincent, Hoch, French, Dorati, Muench, Drese, Oeser.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Nov) (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Items 1-30. Primary correspondents: Chagrin, Mills Music, Drese, Draeger, Westerman, Litowchak, Worner, Strecker, Edwards, Roseman, Mottier.
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Dec) (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Items 31-60. Primary correspondents: Auras, Roseman, Seder, Strecker, Lazare, Rink, Westerman, Draeger, Bauer, Mills Music, Allison,Hilb, Kousssevitzky, Guthind, Lewertoff.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Jan) (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Items 61-90. Primary correspondents: Lazare, Trotter, Stone, Rink, Dorati, Oeser, Eichrodt, Hirth, Mills Music, Westerman, Seder, Schilder, Korngold, Vincent, Braunschweig.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Jan-Feb) (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Items 91-120. Primary correspondents: Vincent, Bogan, Mottier, Gerstley, Selma, Draeger, Solomon, Villurci, Gefen, Isaacs, Klauss, Rosenblith, Lazare, Leonard, Westerman.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Feb-Mar) (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Items 121-150. Primary correspondents: Bass, Hoch, Strecker, Auras, Finkelstein, Steinberg, Dorati, Copland, Commings, Roseman, Brouwning, Munch, Westerman, Stummvoll.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Mar) (Box 65, Folder 6)
    Items 151-180. Primary correspondents: Vincent, Lazare, Rittmann, Hilb, Golschmann, Copland, Steinberg, Ussachevsky, Munch, Cummings, Denham, Strecker, Robbins, Solow, Seder, Robbins, Rosenblith.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Mar) (Box 65, Folder 7)
    Items 181-210. Primary correspondents: Rosenblith, De Barenne, Golschmann, Steinberg, Westermann, Ussachevsky, Vincent, Sinzheimer, Schott, Oeser, Castelnuovo-Tedesco.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Apr) (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Items 1-30. Primary correspondents: Lazare, AMP, Mills Music, Dorati, Sinzheimer, Ussachevsky, Vincent, Nevins, Josephson, Sweeney, Braunschweig, Steinberg, Schott, Huebner.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (May) (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Items 31-60. Primary correspondents: Steinberg, Oeser, Griller, Dorati, Mann, Braunschweig, Lehner, Vincent.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (May-Jun) (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Items 61-90. Primary correspondents: Bass, Lazare, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mills Music, Griller, Strecker, Bard, Braunschweig, Auras, Hoch, Rutz, Mottier.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Jun-Jul) (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Items 91-120. Primary correspondents: Mills Music, Braunschweig, Mottier, Hoch, Lazare, Griller, Dorati, Cummings, Schwartz, Auras, Kendall, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Jul-Aug) (Box 66, Folder 5)
    Items 121-150. Primary correspondents: Seder, Kendall, Braunschweig, Mills Music, Mottier, Amlinger, Fraenkel, Rebner, Zoff, Lazare.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Aug) (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Items 151-180. Primary correspondents: Mills Music, Schott, Lazare, Meissner, Sokoloff, Bianca, Dorati.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Sep) (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Items 181-210. Primary correspondents: Mills Music, Rebner, Moller, Dorati, Mercury Records, Korn, Koussevitzky, Pritchard, Steinberg, Rittmann.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Sep-Oct) (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Items 1-30. Primary correspondents: Geohr, Stolper, Cohn, Koussevitsky, Pritchard, Gruen, Halusa, Wright, Jackson, Braunschweig, Steinberg, Dorati, Stark.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Oct-Nov) (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Items 31-60. Primary correspondents: Korn, Cohn, Stark, Wright, Guy, Jackson, Kendall, Lopatnikoff, Dorati, Braunschweig, Schott, Gilbert, Schiff.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Nov-Dec) (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Items 61-90. Primary correspondents: Reifferscheidt, Auras, Heuss, J.S. Trotter, Kaufman, Poduschka, Hartford, Frankenau, Salzman, Steinberg, Ziegler, Strecker, Dorati, Kuhn.
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Dec & n.d.) - 1958 (Jan) (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Items 91-120. Primary correspondents: Korn, Kuhn, Steinberg, Dorati, Castelnouvo-Tedesco, Bianca, Bauer, Auras, Hirth, Sokoloff, Westerman, Trotter, Hartford, Braunschweig, Izant, Jackson, Feilbogen, Beer, Schott, Wright, Hargreaves, Weschler.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Feb) (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Items 121-150. Primary correspondents: Epstein, Korn, Beer, Braunschweig, Schwartz, Westerman, Wright, Sweeney, Westerdahl, Leibgold, Trotter, Salzer, Jackson, Mahler-Werfel, Poduschka.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Feb-Mar) (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Items 151-180. Primary correspondents: Weinberger, Westerman, Mills, Wright, Trotter, Schwartz, Jackson, Flor, Hoch, Poduschka, Cohn, Schweitzer, Solomon, Lerner, Korns, Niederost, Pietsch, Rebner, Heuss, Reitz.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Mar-Apr) (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Items 181-211. Primary correspondents: Lerner, Dorati, Jackson, Jung, Sweeney, Goldstein, Wright, Frenkel, Heuss, Flor, Huttenback, Weinberger, Bass, Braunschweig, Strecker, Brenn, Sokoloff, Byrns, Walters, Hilb.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Apr) (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Items 1-30. Primary correspondents: Cole, Braunschweig, Moldenhauer, Wunsch, Schott, Dorati, Lerner, Byrns, Trotter, Huttenback, Hausswald, Pietsch, Ben-Gavriel, Schwartz, Auras, Hilb, Strecker, Westerman.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Apr-May) (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Items 31-60. Primary correspondents:Steinberg, Braunschweig, Hans, Farmer, Huttenback, Jackson, Tedesco, Jackson, Stark, Ben-Gavriel, Abbey, Cohn, Byrns, Goldstein, Hilb.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (May-Jun) (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Items 61-90. Primary correspondents: Byrns, Stillman, Stark, Albert, Pietsch, Huttenback, Trotter, Stark, Forster, Jackson, Westerman, Braunschweig, Moldenhauer, Hausswald, Wright, Bass, Ziegler, Hoch.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (June) (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Items 91-120. Primary correspondents: Cummings, Braunschweig, Hempfinger, Hoch, Stark, Lazare, Worner, Poduschka, Jackson, Forster, Bass, Munch, Leinsdorff, ALACA, Schott, Wright, Rosenstock, Huttenback.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (July) (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Items 121-150. Primary correspondents: Moldenhauer, Braunschweig, Jackson, ALACA, Kaufman, Huttenback, Abbey, Ebert, Roman, Sweeney, Westerman, Geiseler, MacDowell, Stark, Schiff, Wright.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Jul-Aug) (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Items 151-180. Primary correspondents: Jackson, Cohn, Geiseler, Braunschweig, Trotter, Schiff, Ebert, Kendall, Cummings, Wright, Stark, Eichrodl, Braunschweig, Sargent, Bass, Jackson, Huttenback, MacDowell.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Aug-Sep) (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Items 181-211. Primary correspondents: Huttenback, Schwartz, Leuckhart, Geiseler, Strecker, Schiff, Cohn, Westerman, Sasse, Wiener, Abbey, Schaal, Franzi, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Sep-Oct) (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Items 1-30. Primary correspondents: Mills, Stolper, Schwartz, Rink, Vincent, Franzi, Schall, Kroll, Schiff, Roseman, Welsch, Jones, Rink, Ostland, Jackson.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Oct-Dec) (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Items 31-60. Primary correspondents: Beer, Schiff, Westerman, Vincent, Schueler, Rosebaud, Hasse, Geiseler, Izant, Reutter, Byrns.
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Dec) - 1959 (Feb) (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Items 61-90. Primary correspondents: Klingner, Hartford, Brenn, Auras, Cohn, Rosebaud, Stolper, Dorati, Weyl, Mottier, Sraunschweig, Westerman, Cohn, Smith, Graf, Feiseler.
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Feb-May) (Box 69, Folder 4)